[
    {
        "question": "B3 on string 5",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "C4 on string 5",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "C#4 on string 5",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "D4 on string 5",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "D#4 on string 5",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "E4 on string 5",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "F4 on string 5",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "F#4 on string 5",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "G4 on string 5",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "G#4 on string 5",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "A4 on string 5",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "A#4 on string 5",
        "answer": "11"
    }	
]
